(忆往昔)
这些特有的征兆  它们预示着什么
And these specific omens -- they're prelude to what?
天启四骑士
The four horsemen.
-哪个骑士是骑红马的呢  - 战争骑士
- And which one rides the red horse?  - War.
孩子们  你们杀不死战争骑士的
You can't kill war, kiddos.
这我们知道
Oh, we know.
戒指  那个戒指
The ring. The ring.
你看到刀刃上淋淋滴落的鲜血
You can't stop thinking about it --
你就一直忍不住的在想它
Ever since you saw it dripping off the blade of that knife.
鲜血  鲜血  鲜血
Blood, blood, blood.
我不是什么伪君子
I'm not some junkie!
我觉得这个迪恩和萨姆的故事真是烂透了
I think that the "Dean and Sam" Story sucks!
这不是什么有趣的事儿
It is not fun.
更不是在娱乐大众
It's not entertaining.
简直就是胡扯瞎掰
It is a river of crap
它会让大多数人被送去精神病院
That would send most people howling to the nuthouse!
你想去拯救多少人呢
How many people do you have to save?
全人类
All of 'em.
你每天怎么能睡得安稳呢
How do you get up in the morning?
真是个好问题
That's a good question.
我只是太累了  兄弟
I'm just tired, man.
我受够了
And I'm done.
我真的受够了
I am just done.
(如今)
第一次约会
First date.
拉塞尔  今晚我过得真开心
I had a really good time tonight, Russell.
爱丽丝
Alice...
我们还能再见吗
Can I see you again?
周日怎么样
Sunday, maybe?
我只是不想孤单
I just don't want to be alone
过情人节
on valentine's day...
又一次这样
Again.
我明白你的意思
I know what you mean.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是  我  不想让你觉得
I just -- I -- I don't want you to think
我是那种人  那种
I'm the type of person who --
不  是我应该道歉
No, I should apologize --
哦  天啊
Oh, god.
我很欣赏你此刻拙劣的表现
I respect the crap out of you right now.
闭嘴吧你
Shut up!
你的脖子!
Your neck!
我想是我咬了你
I think I bit you.
没关系
It's okay.
感觉很爽
It's good.
啊  我曾经如此的孤单
Ugh! I've been so alone.
那么空虚
So empty...
我知道  我也是
I know. Me too.
我想要你  拉塞尔
I want you, Russell --
要你的全部融入我的躯体
All of you... inside me...
好的
Yes.
那么
So...
是你发现尸体的吗
You were the one who found the bodies?
当时到处都是血
There was blood everywhere...
另外还有一些器官
And...other stuff...
我觉得当时爱丽丝已经死了
I think Alice was already dead.
但是拉塞尔没死吗
But Russell wasn't?
他也奄奄一息了
I think he was, mostly,
除了  他还有一点点的
Except... he was still sort of...
咀嚼动作
Chewing a little.
天啊
Oh.
两个人怎么可能做这种事
How do two people even do that --
互相撕咬直到死亡
Eat each other to death?
真是一个好问题
That's a really good question.
最近一些日子
Now, the last few days,
你注意到她有什么反常表现吗
Did you notice her acting erratically?
你是什么意思
How do you mean?
我的意思是她是不是有点儿
I mean, did she seem...
反常好斗的敌对情绪
Unusually hostile, aggressive?
这不可能
No way.
爱丽丝滴酒不沾  甚至从不骂人
Alice never drank, never even swore.
她是个好姑娘
She was a nice girl.
正如我说的  这个好女孩
And I'm talking, like, a nice girl --
她还留着她的誓盟戒呢
Like she still had her promise ring,
如果你明白我的意思的话
If you know what I mean.
她是个处女啊
She was a virgin?
坚决抵制婚前性行为
No premarital.
我曾经还纳闷她是怎么能做到的呢
I used to wonder how she did it.
我的意思是  不做那个
I mean, you know, didn't do it.
这是她数月里第一次约会
It was her first date in months.
她当时那么的兴奋
She was so excited.
显然  他们俩个都很兴奋
Apparently, they were both pretty excited.
情况如何
How'd it go?
没有异常电场  也没有硫磺
No EMF, no sulfur.
貌似既不是幽灵和恶鬼附身
Ghost possession and demonic possession
两者都不是
are both probably out.
那你让我压哪一个啊
Hmm. That's where I was puttin' my money.
都不是
Nope.
好吧  然后怎样
Well, then what, then?
哦  老兄
Oh, dude!
墙角那儿  你没见着那些尸体
At the coroner's -- you didn't see these bodies.
这俩人互相撕咬咬
I mean, these two started eating
他们就这么一直咬
A-and they just... kept going.
然后他们的胃塞满了
I mean, their stomachs were full.
就像吃感恩节晚餐那么撑
Like -- like... thanksgiving-dinner full.
真是相依为命
Talk about co-dependent.
那么
Well...
我们已经去看过了
I mean, we got our feelers out.
今晚也干不了什么别的
Not much more we can do tonight.
好吧
All right.
我来查查资料
I'm just gonna go through some files.
你想去哪儿就去吧
You can go ahead and get going.
什么
Sorry?
去吧  释放你的饥渴
Go ahead. Unleash the kraken.
明天早上见
See you tomorrow morning.
我上哪去
Where am I going?
迪恩  今天是情人节
Dean, it's valentine's day.
你最喜欢的节日  记起来了吗
Your favorite holiday, remember?
你老管它叫什么来着
I mean, what do you always call it --
自由浪子的圣诞节
Uh, unattached drifter christmas?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
嗯  确实是
Well... be that as it may...
我不知道
I don't know.
也许今年没那个心情吧
Guess I'm not feeling it this year.
那你不去逛满是单身女人酒吧了吗
So you're not into bars full of lonely women?
不去了吧
Nah, I guess not.
怎么了
What?
就像狗不吃屎了一样
It's when a dog doesn't eat --
你是真的觉悟了这样做不对
That's when you know something's really wrong.
非常明显的圣人般的担心又准时出现了
Remarkably patronizing concern duly noted.
没什么不对的  开工还是干吗
Nothing's wrong. We gonna work or what?
真烦  搞什么飞机
Ouch! No me gusta.
你审查过这个吗  小吉
Have you been proofing this thing, Jimbo?
什么
Sorry?
你怎么又在看手机呢
Tell me you are not checking your cellphone again!
伙计  你像被她栓了狗链一样
Man, she's got you on a leash.
我没被栓着  布拉德
I'm not on a leash, brad.
她只是想知道我在哪
She just wants to know where I am.
她想知道你在她掌控之内
She just wants to know that you're whipped.
不是你想的那样
It's not like that.
是啊  是像
Oh, yeah. It's like...
布拉德  等我两分钟
Brad, just give me two minutes.
不行  老兄
No, man. No.
我是这个项目的负责人
I'm the project leader on this thing,
我不会让我的副手
And I'm not gonna half-ass it
被一个才遇见一个礼拜的
Just 'cause my wingman has gone mental
贱人迷住了
Over some chick he met, like, a week ago.
吉姆
Jim?
什么乱七八糟的
Holy crap.
你刚才在哪呢
Where were you?
我明白
I know.
我只是必须得
It's just I had to --
吉姆  你爱工作多过了我
You can't choose work over me, Jim!
我没有  珍妮斯
I won't, Janice.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry --
小吉  无意冒犯  但说实话老兄
Jimbo, due respect, but honestly, bro --
我们到底要怎样  吉米
What are we gonna do, Jimmy?
我不知道  宝贝儿
I don't know, baby.
像是不管我们怎么做
Seems like whatever we do,
总有些事会把我们分开
Something in life is always gonna keep us apart --
在工作  在家  甚至睡觉的时候
Work, family, sleep.
也许咱们该一起去监狱
Now prison, maybe...
也许吧
Maybe.
但我有个好主意
But I think I have an idea...
怎么样我们才能在一起
How we can stay together...
永远在一起
Forever...
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯  我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
马雷探员  你总是适时出现
Agent Marley, you just can't stay away.
听说你又接到了一宗情侣自杀
Heard you tagged another double suicide.
是啊  我刚把他们装起来
Well, I just finished closing them up.
科尔曼医生  这是我搭档  克里夫探员
Dr. Corman, this is my partner, special agent Cliff.
你好  克里夫探员
Agent Cliff.
我做完了初步尸检
I've finished my prelims.
我摘下那些器官送去做毒理检验
I pulled the organ sets and sent off the tox samples.
好的  你不介意我们看看尸体吧
Great. You mind if we take a look at the bodies?
不介意
Not at all.
但是就像我说的
But like I said --
他们最新鲜饱满的部分都已经装盒了
Their...good-and-plenties are already tupperwared.
真棒
Super.
钥匙交给前台的马蒂
Leave the keys with Marty up front.
别忘了  绅士们
And please, gentlemen...
打开之后记得冷冻
Refrigerate after opening...
做我的爱人吧
Be my valentine?
哇哦  等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a second.
这些心脏都有一样的标记
These hearts both have identical marks.
看看这个
Check this out.
像是某个字母
It looks like some kind of letter.
不会吧
Oh, no.
怎么了
What?
我觉得这个是以诺克符咒
I think it's Enochian.
你是说那种天使抓痕吗
You mean like angel scratches?
就像咱俩肋骨上刻的那东西吗
So you think it's like the tagging on our ribs?
迪恩  我不知道
Dean, I don't know.
见鬼
Ah, hell.
卡西  我是迪恩
Cass, it's Dean.
对  圣詹姆斯医疗中心
Yeah, room 31-c, basement level...
地下一层  31-C房间
St. James medical center.
我到了
I'm there now.
是  我看出来了
Yeah, I get that.
那我就  挂电话了
I'm gonna hang up now.
好
Right.
你说的对  萨姆  这些是天使的记号
You're right, Sam. These are angelic marks.
我想另外那些心脏上面
I imagine you'll find similar marks
也会有类似的记号
on the other couples' hearts as well --
那到底是什么  那记号什么意思
So, what are they? I mean, what do they mean?
那是结合记号
It's a mark of union.
这对男女本来想进行交配的
This man and woman were intended to mate.
好吧  那记号是谁弄上去的
Okay, but who put them there?
你们人类称他们为"丘比特"
Well, your people call them "Cupid."
什么
A what?
人类的神话中记载丘比特属于低等天使
What human myth has mistaken for "Cupid"
这是错误的
is actually a lower order of angel.
严格来说  他们是小天使  第三阶天使
Technically it's a cherub, third-class.
小天使
Cherub?
对  他们无处不在
Yeah, they're all over the world.
数量很多
There are dozens of them.
你是说那个裹着尿布飞来飞去的小胖孩
You mean the little flying fat kid in diapers?
他们并没有失禁
They're not incontinent.
好  不论如何
Okay, anyways.
所以你的意思是
So, what you're saying --
我的意思是  有一个丘比特在人间作乱
What I'm saying is a Cupid has gone rogue.
在他再次杀戮之前  我们必须阻止他
and we have to stop him -- before he kills again.
相当合理
Naturally.
当然得阻止他
Of course we do.
怎么  你碰巧知道
So, what, you just happen to know
他喜欢这里大波斯菊是吗
he likes the cosmos at this place?
这里是人类进行繁殖的中心地带
This place is a nexus of human reproduction.
绝对吻合丘比特
It's exactly the kind of --
选择传播情欲地点的标准
...of garden the Cupid will come to -- to pollinate.
等等
Wait a minute.
你不饿吗
You're not hungry?
不饿啊
No.
干嘛  我不饿啊
What? I'm not hungry.
这么说你不吃了吧
Then you're not gonna finish that?
他来了
He's here.
在哪
Where?
我什么也没看见
I don't see anything.
在那儿
There.
你是说坐在同一侧的那对情侣吗
You mean the same-side-of-the-booth couple over there?
我们后面见
Meet me in the back.
卡西  他在哪儿
Cass, where is he?
我困住他了
I have him tethered.
[咒语]
显露真身吧
Manifest yourself.
他在哪儿
So, where is he?
我在这儿呐
Here I am!
救命啊
Help!
噢哟  救援马上就到
Oh, help is on the way.
就来了哟  就来了哟
Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
你好呀
Hello, you!
这就是丘比特
This is Cupid?
是
Yes.
再瞧瞧你
And look at you, huh?
-不要  - 要的
- No. - Yes!
要的要的要的
Yes, yes, yes!
这是开战了吗  我们要开打了吗
Is this a fight? Are we in a fight?
这是他们的  问好方式
This is... their handshake.
-我不喜欢  - 没人喜欢
- I don't like it. - No one likes it.
我有什么可以帮你们的
What can I do for you?
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
做什么
Doing what?
你的目标  那些被你标记的人
Your targets -- the ones you've marked --
他们在互相屠杀
they're slaughtering each other.
什么
What?
是吗
They are?
听着  小裸男
Listen, birthday suit,
我们都知道了
We know, okay?
我们知道你满世界乱飞
We know you been flittin' around,
用你那个毒箭对人们乱射一气
popping people with your poison arrow,
让他们互相残杀
making them murder each other!
我们不知道你为什么这么做
What we don't know is why.
你以为我
You think that I --
这个
Well, uh...
我不知道说什么好
I don't know what to say.
是不是
Should...
是不是得过去个人  劝劝他
Should somebody maybe... go talk to him?
对  好主意  好好表现  卡西
Yeah, that's a good idea. Give 'em hell, Cass.
听着
Um...look.
我们不是故意要
We didn't mean to, um...
要伤害你的感情
...hurt your feelings.
爱情对我来说不是一个词能描述的
Love is more than a word to me, you know.
我爱爱情  我爱它
I love love. I love it!
如果这是不对的  就让我错下去吧
And if that's wrong, I don't want to be right!
是的  好的  当然
Yes, yes. Of course.
我
I, uh...
我不知道你在说些什么
I have no idea what you're saying.
我刚刚正在我指定的地点巡逻
I was just on my appointed rounds.
无论那之后我的目标是什么
Whatever my targets do after that,
这跟我没关系
That's nothing to do with me.
我  我只是听从了命令
I-I was following my orders.
求你了  兄弟  阅读我的思想
Please, brother. Read my mind.
快读我的思想  你就会明白了
Read my mind. You'll see.
他说的是真话
He's telling the truth.
谢天谢地  谢谢你
Jiminy christmas. Thank you.
等等  你刚刚说
Wait, wait, you said --
你说你只是听从了命令
You said you were just following orders?
谁的命令
Whose orders?
上天的命令  傻瓜  上天啊
Heaven, silly. Heaven.
为什么上天会关心
Why does heaven care
哈里和萨莉是否相遇
If harry meets sally?
一般情况下来说  他们不会
Oh, mostly they don't.
某种血缘关系  某种命运
You know, certain bloodlines, certain destinies.
-就像你们一样  - 什么
- Oh, like yours.  - What?
是的  约翰和玛丽·温彻斯特的结合
Yeah, the union of John and Mary Winchester --
天造的一对  最优先的安排
Very big deal upstairs, top priority arrangement. Mm.
是你撮合了我们的父母
Are you saying that you fixed-up our parents?
不是我  但是  也算是我
Well, not me, but...yeah.
这也不简单
Well, it wasn't easy, either.
一开始他们不能相互忍受对方
Ooh, they couldn't stand each other at first.
但是当我们把事处理好后
But when we were done with them --
他们成了完美的一对
Perfect couple.
-完美  - 是啊
- Perfect?  - Yeah.
他们死了
They're dead
很抱歉  但是  命令说的很清楚
I'm sorry, but... the orders were very clear.
你和萨姆需要出生
You and sam needed to be born.
你们的父母是
Your parents were just, uh...
命中注定的
Meant to be.
天造地设的一对
A match made in heaven
天生的
Heaven!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
他去哪儿了
Where is he?
他人呢
Where'd he go?!
我想你把他惹恼了
I believe you upset him.
把他惹恼了
Upset him?!
迪恩  够了
Dean. Enough!
什么
What?
你刚刚给了丘比特一拳
You just punched a Cupid!
我打的是一个混蛋
I punched a dick!
我们要不要谈谈
Are we gonna talk about
是什么把你惹火了
What's been up with you lately or not?
还是不了
Or not.
你说你们要听听
You said you wanted to hear about
其他一些怪异的消息
Any other weird ones.
好的
Okay.
莱斯特·芬奇
Lester Finch.
看看他的诊断记录
Pulled his records.
这位先生之前大概有400磅重
Looks like this gentleman used to weigh 400 pounds or so,
直到他做了一次胃绕道手术
Till he got a gastric bypass,
这让他的体重下降明显
Which brought down his weight considerably.
但是昨晚  由于某些原因
But then for some reason, last night,
他没有节制的吃奶油蛋糕
He decided to go on a twinkie binge.
那么他是死于猛吃蛋糕
So, he died from a twinkie binge?
当他松开了肚子上的腰带之后
Well, after he blew out the band around his stomach,
他把胃填得直到破裂
He filled it up till it burst.
但是他不能再咽下食物了
but he can no longer swallow,
他开始用一把
He started jamming the cakes down his gullet
一把马桶刷
With a...
把蛋糕塞进他的咽喉
With a toilet brush,
就像他吃了一颗炸弹
Like he was ramrodding a cannon.
那你准备怎么做
So, what do you make of it?
我说过这是
I'd say that it was
一件非常罕见的事
A very peculiar thing to do...
这家伙没有被丘比特标记
So, uh, this guy was not marked by Cupid,
但是他的死确实很可疑
But his death is definitely suspicious.
我刚刚看了一下警察的记事簿
Yeah, well, I just went through the police blotter,
数了一下
And counting him,
从星期三起有8起自杀案
That's eight suicides since wednesday
19起连环杀人案
AND 19 O.D.S --
这远远高于一般的恶灵致死案件
That's way out of the seasonal batting average.
如果有一个固定模式的话
Yeah, if there's a pattern here,
那就不仅仅是关于爱情了
it ain't just love.
这会远远超出我们所想象的
It's a hell of a lot bigger than we thought.
那好  我们10点见
Yeah, all right. I'll see you in 10.
嗯  好的
Yeah, okay.
该死的  我知道你是什么了
I know what you are, damn it.
我能感觉到你
I could smell you.
温彻斯特
Winchester.
那恶魔到底为什么要这么做
What the hell does a demon got to do with this, anyway?
相信我  我也没有头绪
Believe me, I got no idea.
你没事吧
You okay?
是的  是的  我会没事的
Yeah, yeah. I'll be all right.
我们来打开她吧
Let's crack her open.
看看还有什么更坏的事在等着  好吗
What's the worst that could happen, right?
那到底是什么东西
What the hell was that?
是一个人类的灵魂
It's a human soul.
终于开始露出点眉目了
It's starting to make sense.
那么  什么叫露出点眉目了
Now, what about that makes sense?
还有你什么时候开始吃东西了
And when did you start eating?
没错
Exactly.
我的饥饿  其实就是条线索
My hunger -- it's a clue, actually.
-关于什么的  - 关于什么的
- For what? - For what?
这座小镇不是遭到什么
This town is not suffering
爱恨情仇的影响
From some love-gone-wrong effect.
而是肚子饿了
It's suffering from hunger.
应该说是饥饿
Starvation, to be exact --
具体点就是
Specifically...
饥荒
Famine.
Famine?
四骑士之一
A-as in the horseman?
太好了
Great.
真  真是棒极了
T-t-that's freaking great.
在我看来饥荒就是肚子饿
I thought famine meant starvation,
就像  你所知道的  想吃东西
Like as in, you know, food.
对  完全正确
Yes. Absolutely.
但不仅仅是食物
But not just food.
而是每个人都会对一些事物非常的饥渴
I mean, everyone seems to be starving for something --
性  关注  毒品  爱情
Sex, attention, drugs, love...
那就可以解释
Well, that explains
为什么丘比特选了那对小情侣
The puppy-lovers that Cupid shot up.
是的
Right.
小天使让那俩人对爱情产生渴望
The cherub made them crave love,
饥荒接着到来  然后使他们对爱情发狂
And then famine came, and made them rabid for it.
好的  那么你呢
Okay, but what about you?
我是说  小天使什么时候开始
I mean, since when do angels
悄悄的开始啃白色城堡了
Secretly hunger for white castle?
是我的皮囊  吉米
It's my vessel -- Jimmy.
他开始对肉狂热了
His, uh, appetite for red meat
他也被饥荒之魔触碰到了
Has been touched by famine's effect.
所以  饥荒席卷了整个小镇
So, famine just rolls into town
然后每个人都变的疯狂了
And everybody goes crazy?
随后饥荒之魔跨着黑色的骏马
"And then will come famine riding on a black steed."
踏遍整个大陆
"He will ride into the land of plenty..."
万物皆因骑士之饥而被吞噬
"...and great will be the horseman's hunger,
只因他的饥饿
For he is hunger."
他的饥饿弥漫在空气中  笼罩在人群里
"His hunger will seep out and poison the air."
饿啊
Hungry.
饥荒饿了
Famine's hungry.
他得吞食那些被害者的灵魂
He must devour the souls of his victims.
那么  那个手提箱里装的是
So, that's what was in the briefcase --
那个奶油公子的灵魂
The twinkie dude's soul?
路西法派出他的恶魔手下们照看着饥荒
Lucifer has sent his demons to care for famine,
喂好他  为了确保他时刻准备好
To feed him, make certain he'll be ready.
准备好什么
Ready for what?
准备好征服整个大陆
To march across the land.
饿啊
Hungry.
萨姆·温彻斯特  那个皮囊
Sam winchester -- the vessel --
他来了
He's here.
-在哪  - 医院里
- Where? - At the hospital.
我们打了一架  但被他跑了
We fought, but he got away.
我
I...
我从他身上拿到了这个
I got this off him.
很好  是的
Good. Yes.
但要先吃午餐
After lunch.
现在  食物在哪里
Now, where is it?
抱歉
Sorry?
那个爱吃奶油蛋糕的人
The one who loves cream cake so much.
他的灵魂在哪里
Where is his soul?
很抱歉  不  那个
I am sorry. No. The --
温彻斯特把箱子抢走了
Winchester took the case from me.
呃  他拿着那把刀
Uh, he had the knife.
我
I --
我给丢了
I lost it.
但我很饿
But I'm hungry!
我再去找一个  十分钟就能搞定
I'll get another. I-I won't be 10 minutes.
饿啊  我现在就要
Hungry! Now!
美  味  啊
Delicious!
饥荒
Famine?
是的
Yes.
那么  这整个小镇
So, what, this whole town
就去狂吃  狂喝  然后就都撑死了
Is just gonna eat, drink, and screw itself to death?
我们得去阻止它
We should stop it.
是啊  想法真不错
Yeah, that's a great idea.
怎么阻止呢
How?
上一次遇见骑士时  你是怎么阻止他的
How did you stop the last horseman you met?
战争的魔咒在这个戒指里
War got his mojo from this ring.
我们把他的手指切下后
And after we cut it off,
他就夹着尾巴逃跑了
he just tucked tail and ran.
那些遭受饥荒影响的人们
And everybody that was affected,
仿佛是从梦中惊醒
it was like they woke up out of a dream.
你认为饥荒骑士也有个类似的戒指吗
You think famine's got a class ring, too?
我知道他有
I know he does.
好吧
Well, okay.
那我们去找到他  并把他的手指剁了
Let's track him down and get to chopping.
好的
Yeah.
你怎么了  变成汉堡神偷了吗
What are you, the hamburglar?
(麦当劳动画人物  酷爱汉堡)
我已经喜欢上牛肉堡了
I've developed a taste for ground beef.
你有没有想过克制住呢
Well, have you even tried to stop it?
我是天使  可以想停就停
I'm an angel. I can stop anytime I want.
想停就停
Whatever.
萨姆  我们出发吧
Sam, let's roll.
迪恩
Dean...
我
I, um...
我不能
I can't.
我不能走
I can't go.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我想我已受饥荒影响了  迪恩
I think it got to me, Dean.
我很饿
I think I'm hungry for it...
对什么产生饥饿
Hungry for what?
你知道的
You know.
恶魔之血吗
Demon blood?
你开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
你得把他弄走
You got to get him out of here.
你得把他送走  送去蒙大拿州吧
You got to beam him to, like, Montana.
只要离开这儿随便哪儿
Anywhere but here.
没用的  他已经被传染了
It won't work. He's already infected.
饥饿感会在他全身蔓延
The hunger is just gonna travel with him.
那我们该怎么办
Well, then, what do we do?
你去把那个混蛋的手指砍了
You go cut that bastard's finger off.
你听到了吧
You heard him.
可是...  迪恩
But, Dean...
你在离开前  你最好...
Before you go, you better...
你最好把我锁起来
...you better lock me down.
这样最好
But good.
好了  你在这儿等会儿
All right, well, just hang in there.
我们会尽快回来的
We'll be back as soon as we can.
小心点
Be careful.
还有  快去快回
And...hurry.
嘿  马蒂
Hey, Marty.
科尔曼医生在吗
Is Dr. Corman around?
你们还没听说吗
You haven't heard?
什么
Heard what?
这20年来他一直都恪尽职守
Guy's been dry for the last 20 years,
可今天早上  他突然离开工作岗位
But this morning, he left work,
回家以后  酗酒过量而死
went home, and drank himself to death.
-是饥荒骑士  - 什么
- It's famine.  - Pardon?
能容许我们单独聊会儿吗
Would you give us a minute, please?
好的
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
妈的
Crap!
我真的有点喜欢上他了
I really kind of liked this guy.
他们还没有夺去他的灵魂
They haven't harvested his soul yet.
如果我们想用"追魂法"抓住饥荒骑士
Well, if we want to play "Follow the soul" to get to famine,
我们最好从这名医生开始调查
Our best shot starts with the doc, here.
你不是吧
Are you serious?
这些食物
These make me...
让我愉悦万分啊
...very happy.
你吃了多少个了
How many is that?
我忘了
I lost count.
一两百个吧
It's in the low hundreds.
我不明白的是
What I don't understand is...
迪恩  你怎么会不饿呢
Where is your hunger, Dean?
虽然进程缓慢
Well, slowly but surely,
镇上的人最终都会成为饥荒骑士的牺牲品
everyone in this town is falling prey to famine,
可到目前为止你似乎丝毫未受影响
but so far, you seem unaffected.
当我想喝的时候  我就喝
Hey, when I want to drink, I drink.
想做爱就做爱
When I want sex, I go get it.
至于吃三明治和打架也是同理
Same goes for a sandwich or a fight.
那么
So...
你是说你的适应能力强吗
You're saying you're just well-adjusted?
天  当然不是  我只是吃饱喝足了
God, no. I'm just well-fed.
他来了
There.
伙计们
Guys?
伙计们  怎么回事
Guys, what happened?
我觉得这样没用
I don't think it worked.
我觉得我还是...
I think I'm still --
我还是饿
...still hungry.
瞧啊
Look at this.
有人帮我们把你捆起来了
Someone trussed you up for us.
老大说要留你活口
Boss says we can't kill you...
不过我想我们可以把你切成几块带给他
...but I bet we can break off a few pieces.
还没轮到你
Wait your turn.
恶魔
Demons.
要把计划再复习一遍吗
You want to go over the plan again?
(麦当劳儿童套餐)
开心乐园餐
Hey, happy meal.
什么计划
The plan?
我拿着刀进去
I take the knife, I go in,
把饥荒骑士戴戒指的手指砍下来
I cut off the ring hand of famine,
然后返回停车场见你
And I meet you back here in the parking lot.
听上去挺简单
Well, that sounds foolproof.
时间太长了吧
This is taking too long.
卡西
Cass!
Cass.
另一位温彻斯特先生
The other Mr. Winchester.
你对他做了什么
What did you do to him?
你放狗咬我
You sicced your dog on me.
我只是赏他了一块骨头
I just threw him a steak.
这就是你的了不起的招数
So this is your big trick?
让人们为可可泡芙发疯
Making people cuckoo for cocoa puffs?
没有费我多少神  只是助推了一下
Doesn't take much -- hardly a push.
美国人一直都是"吃到饱"
Oh, America -- all-you-can-eat, all the time.
吃啊  喝啊
Consume, consume.
一群穿肥裤子的蝗虫
A swarm of locusts in stretch pants.
可你们还是饥饿
And yet, you're all still starving
因为饿不仅仅来自于身体
Because hunger doesn't just come from the body,
还来自于灵魂
It also comes from the soul.
真好笑  我的怎么就没有
It's funny, it doesn't seem to be coming from mine.
是呀
Yes.
我注意到了
I noticed that.
你知道这是为什么吗
Have you wondered why that is?
在我出现的地方  你怎么还能正常
How you could even walk in my presence?
我觉得
Well, I like to think
是由于我的人格力量
It's because of my strength of character.
我不赞同
I disagree.
是的
Yes.
我知道了
I see.
那里深邃  黑暗
That's one deep, dark
迪恩  你心里什么也没有
nothing you got there, Dean.
你什么都放不进去  不是吗
Can't fill it, can you?
不是用食物或酒
Not with food or drink.
甚至连性都没有
Not even with sex.
你满口废话
Oh, you're so full of crap.
你可以装傻  对你弟弟开玩笑  欺骗他
Oh, you can smirk and joke and lie to your brother,
欺骗自己  但你骗不了我
Lie to yourself, but not to me!
迪恩  我可以看见你的内心
I can see inside you, Dean.
我可以看见
I can see
你是多么的支离破碎
how broken you are,
多么的挫败
How defeated.
你赢不了  你知道的
You can't win, and you know it.
但是你还是坚持战斗
But you just keep fighting.
机械的战斗
Just...keep going through the motions.
你不饿  迪恩  因为
You're not hungry, dean, because inside,
你的心
You're already...
早死了
Dead.
放他走
Let him go.
萨姆
Sam...
萨姆  不要
Sammy, no!
住手
Stop!
谁也不许动这个可爱的小男孩一根毫毛
No one lays a finger on this sweet little boy.
萨姆  你吃了我送你的点心
Sam, I see you got the snack I sent you.
你送来的
You sent?
别担心  你和其他人不同
Don't worry. You're not like everyone else.
你不会因为喝得太多而死
You'll never die from drinking too much.
你是一个例外
You're the exception that proves the rule.
撒旦
Just the way...
想要你成为那样的人
Satan wanted you to be.
那么
So...
割开他们的喉咙
...cut their throats.
享用他们
Have at them!
萨姆  不要
Sammy, no!
请把  不要客气
Please, be my guest.
不要
No.
那么
Well...
好吧
Fine.
要是你不要他们
If you don't want them...
那他们就归我了
Then I'll have them.
萨姆  我是天启骑士
I'm a horseman, Sam.
你的能力对我不起作用
Your power doesn't work on me.
说的对
You're right.
但是对他们起作用
But it will work on them.
伙计们  求你们啦
Guys, help!
在里面的那个人不是他
That's not him in there.
不是真正的他
Not really.
我知道
I know.
迪恩  萨姆得从这个状态摆脱出来
Dean, Sam just has to get it out of his system.
不然他会
Then he'll be --
听着  我想
Listen, I just, uh...
我得出去透口气
I just need to get some air.
拜托了
Please...
我不能
I can't...
帮帮我吧
I need some help.
求你了
Please?